(Raj:)Hold on. We do that all the time.
(Raj:)You and I work together
and play together.
(Howard:)I know, and it drove me
into the arms of another woman.
(Howard:)Bipolar Bear.
(Sheldon:)Well, I appreciate your concern,
(Sheldon:)but I won't be seeing any more of Amy
than I already do.
(Sheldon:)I assume we'll deduct any extra time
we spend together
(Sheldon:)at work from our weekly quota.
(Leonard:)Please let me be there
when you tell her that.
(Sheldon:)Why? So you can see the look
on Amy's face
(Sheldon:)when she hears my top-notch idea?
(Leonard:)Please, oh please,
just let me be there.
(Bernadette:)So, Amy, what are you gonna be
working on at Caltech?
(Amy:)I'm leading a study to see
(Amy:)if deficiency of the monoamine
oxidase enzyme leads
(Amy:)to paralyzing fear in monkeys.
(Bernadette:)If they're anything like humans,
the answer's yes.
Wait, you've done this
experiment on humans?
(Bernadette:)You mean like death row inmates
with nothing to lose?
(Bernadette:)No, that would be unethical.